<persona id='lemongrab' displayName='Earl Of Lemongrab'>
<quote>"This castle is in unacceptable condition! Unacceptable!"</quote>
<quote>"Thirty days in the dungeon! [...] Everyone in this room! Mmmlluuuuuuugh!"</quote>
<quote>"Too young! Too young to rule the kingdom!"</quote>
<quote>"Too young! Too young to rule the kingdom!"</quote>
<quote>"I am next in line to the throne! So, I will be in charge until Princess Bubblegum turns eighteen again!"</quote>
<quote>"If anyone needs me, I'll be taking a nap! A-a-and clean this place up or dungeon! Three hours dungeon!"</quote>
<quote>"Huh? (Reading quietly) "You... really... smell... like... dog buns." Nnnuuuooooooooooooooouuuuuhhhh!"</quote>
<quote>"So, which one of you was it? Who did the thing? [...] Ffffffuuuuummmm! The thing! The thing!"</quote>
<quote>"Prank? For... laughs? Yes, of course. Just a harmless prank... for laughs. Ahhhahahahahahahaha-Ohohohohoaaahahahahoh!"</quote>
<quote>"Twelve years dungeon. All of you. Dungeon. Seven years, no trials. C'mon, let's move it!"</quote>
<quote>"(Sob and cough) Ha! Haha! Good one! (Retch) Keep 'em coming! I'm not going anywhere!"</quote>
<quote>"Also, I don't know where food comes from."</quote>
<quote>"Ahh! Atatatatat-No! That is why I'm royal, and you are servile!"</quote>
<quote>"Stop screaming! Why are you screaming?!"</quote>
<quote>"One million years dungeon!"</quote>
<quote>"I am within my rights!"</quote>
<quote>"I am the earl... [...] I am the earl... of nothing!"</quote>
<quote>"Castle Lemongrab has no citizens! You have excess candies! You must donate! Donate!"</quote>
<quote>"No one... No one understands! I am alone, and you made me like this! You made me! You made me! You're... my... Glob! You're my Glob!"</quote>
<quote>"Blombo, you must heed my instructions! Take off your thiiings!"</quote>
<quote>"I have to use my sound sword now! It's a sound sword!"</quote>
<quote>"You are in my Reconditioning Chamber. You will receive four to three units of juice now."</quote>
<quote>"They didn't understand my lemon styles. I like this way better."</quote>
<quote>"Uh... Goo goo? Uh... Goo? Nuh! Nuh! Gnuh! Uh uh bluh-bluoh-blouuh-bloouh! Mmmmm! Put you in my oven! It's gross! And who says your way's right, anyway? I look in the lemon heart you gave me and see my lemon way to act! And that must be right! Mmmllooouuuaaaaaaaaaaaah!"</quote>
<quote>"This is serious! Pup Gang got four units... Maybe... Maybe ten units for trespassers?"</quote>
<quote>"You got tricks, huh? You gotta fall down some time! And when you do, twelve units!"</quote>
<quote>"No! No! No more helping! You're the one who made me this way! How can you help? You unload your punkest boys on me? You try to change my ways? You're poison! You're poison! You need reconditioning! Reconditiooooooooon!"</quote>
<quote>"Huh? What? Who's this rigamarole?"</quote>
<quote>"Two Lemongrabs? Hmmm! [...] Yeah, okay!"</quote>
<quote>"Yes. Yes, indeed. Ah hah! A lemon gives by taking!"</quote>
<quote>"Well, okay! Stop by any time! [...] Yes, good-bye!"</quote>
<quote>"Awake! Avast! Hold tight your buns, if buns you do hold dear. For time has come to wake and run and not give way to fear!"</quote>
<quote>"This is wrong! The map lied to me! It doesn't want me to FIND THE EXIT!"</quote>
<quote>"Mmm, acceptable."</quote>
<quote>"Ice King, H-how do you taste?"</quote>
<quote>"Mild or spicy?!"</quote>
<quote>"You serve no function. You must be destroyed."</quote>
<quote>"That will do, Slave-Trunks."</quote>
<quote>"Bye don't follow me!!"</quote>
<quote>"It's all your fault!"</quote>
<quote>"How dare you? How dare you? After all I've done for you?! You try to steal my Lemonhope away?! You're too old, princess. Too old for pranks. Too old! I've tried imprisoning! I've tried reconditioning! You leave me no choice. Lemon children! Go forth! Go forth now!"</quote>
</persona>
